<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>audioreactive on SHELTRON Visuals</title>
    <link>https://sheltron.netlify.com/categories/audioreactive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in audioreactive on SHELTRON Visuals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheltron.netlify.com/categories/audioreactive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>COLORS</title>
      <link>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2016-10-30-colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2016-10-30-colors/</guid>
      <description>Audio-reactive LED wall Installation with Alex Stickels. Shown at &amp;lsquo;The Art of Dying&amp;rsquo; at The Laundry SF
Using LightJams, programmed a friend&amp;rsquo;s LED wall to be audio reactive to an original orchestral composition. The viewer put on a SubPac and headphones, along with the lightshow it made for a pertty immersive experience! The score had a huge crescendo, which, along with the lights and SubPac shaking your body made for a pretty epic finale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEVELS</title>
      <link>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2016-10-30-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2016-10-30-levels/</guid>
      <description>webgl audio-reactive iterative function system
Live Demo here play it some music with a beat and it should start dancing
while being a TA at Gray Area I worked on a fractal installation that I wanted to be educational.
Background  I had been working with Raymarched Distance Fields for about a year and found a few cool techniques I was happy with:
  raymarching at half-res for performance</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>capyac</title>
      <link>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2015-10-13-capyac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2015-10-13-capyac/</guid>
      <description>Live performance of Audio-Reactive Shaders
VJ for CAPYAC  in 2015 I was lucky enough to meet the talented folks at CAPYAC and become a part of their live show. I use many types of software like VDMX, WebGL and Magic Music Visuals to run custom GLSL shaders and ISF. By hooking a direct audio feed from the stage mixer into the shaders I can get some really responsive audio reactive stuff going on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>