<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>work on SHELTRON Visuals</title>
    <link>https://sheltron.netlify.com/categories/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in work on SHELTRON Visuals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 00:13:37 -0706</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheltron.netlify.com/categories/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>occipital bridge</title>
      <link>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2016-12-21-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2016-12-21-bridge/</guid>
      <description>The First iOS mixed reality headset and rendering engine
Occipital Bridge I made the graphics engine in here, trying to get SceneKit do what it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to with crazy mixed reality rendering and compositing @ 60fps
{% for image in site.static_files %} {% if image.path contains page.imageDir %} {% if myArray contains image.path %} {% else %} {% assign myArray = myArray | push: image.path %} {% endif %} {% endif %} {% endfor %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lynx Laboratories</title>
      <link>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2014-02-01-lynx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 20:32:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2014-02-01-lynx/</guid>
      <description>First realtime mobile 3D scanner
This product was a fully mobile device (box) that could do real-time 3D scanning totally on the device. No cloud or offline processing.
Back at UT I joined a research group called the UT Perception lab. There we worked on realtime 3D reconstruction techniques using GPU processing. I helped implement Kinect Fusion in CUDA, a CUDA raytracer for scanning volume visualizaiton and other 3D reconstruction techniques using heightmaps on manifolds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenSWR</title>
      <link>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2015-10-01-openswr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 20:32:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheltron.netlify.com/portfolio/2015-10-01-openswr/</guid>
      <description>Low-level OpenGL driver development
video: isosurface extraction and realtime rendering of a shit ton of triangles on a xeon phi cluster (no GPUs!)
In 2015 I contracted for Intel&amp;rsquo;s visualization department on an OpenGL driver optimised for many-core intel supercomputer clusters. With that many CPUs, you can treat the network as a GPU, with each core doing some work in a Tile-Based Deferred Rendering (TBDR) pipeline. This was built on the Mesa3D graphics library and greatly improved frame rates on certain systems compared to the built in software renderer in Mesa3D (llvmpipe).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>